productionhub.com 2002-06-03

# ProductionHUB.com

|   
---  

[](https://www.truste.org/validate/10866)ProductionHUB.com is a licensee of the [TRUSTe Privacy Program](http://www.truste.org/). TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This covers the site [www.ProductionHUB.com](http://www.productionhub.com/). Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, ProductionHUB.com has agreed to notify you of:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the web site.
  2. The organization collecting the information.
  3. How is the information used.
  4. With whom the information may be shared.
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under ProductionHUB.com's control
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Bill Williams, Director of Technology by email: [bwilliams@productionhub.com](mailto:bwilliams@productionhub.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question), toll free phone: 877-629-4122 or postal mail: 801 W. Fairbanks Avenue, Winter Park, Florida 32789. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the "[TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog_intro.html)". TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

**What personally identifiable information is collected from you?** back to top

ProductionHUB.com collects a persons name, mailing address, phone number, fax number and e-mail address. We also collect credit card information in order for you to purchase this service. This information is requested during registration and is used to deliver services the user has requested. All other information is optional and is used to create your member profile for other members and users of your community to know more about you, and to better target your interests.

**What are cookies and how are they used?** back to top

A "cookie" identifies your computer to our servers when you visit our site, saving your password so you don't have to reenter information each time you visit. ProductionHUB.com uses cookies to assist the user/member in changing and/or editing their information that is already stored in our database.  The cookie is used to temporarily store the information that the user enters in to our database.  The information is then sent to our support staff to make the necessary changes to your listing.  The benefit of the cookie is that it lets you, the user/member change and/or edit your information online without having to contact a ProductionHUB.com representative.  If you choose not to accept the cookie then you, the user/member must contact the ProductionHUB.com support staff to have the changes and/or edits reflected on your listing. If you'd prefer to refuse cookies, turn them off using your browser. It's not required to have cookies turned on in order to use our web site. 

**The organization collecting the information.** back to top

When you are on ProductionHUB.com and are asked for personal information by productionhub.com, you are sharing that information with productionhub.com only. Please be aware that ProductionHUB.com's advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you on their sites. The information practices of those web sites are not covered by this privacy policy. In addition, users and other members may be able to access certain information that you provide to them (e.g. your e-mail address and content that you post on sites that we link to as well as when you post to the Classifieds section of our website). ProductionHUB.com is not in a position to monitor or control any particular user's or community member's use of that content.

**How the is information used.** back to top

ProductionHUB.com's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the community member, with a potentially fulfilling experience. The more information a user supplies the better potential for maximum benefits.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web user. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. ProductionHub.com utilizes this clear gif on its home page to enable search engine bots or spiders to navigate our site. Most bots are unable to correctly navigate sites with dynamic content such as productionhub.com's. This image is there solely to direct these bots. No information is gathered using this transparent gif and it is in no way tied to users personally identifiable information.

**Log Files**

Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and #of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility called Livestats that uses log files to analyze user movement. See the "Your Profile" section below.

**Tell a Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. ProductionHUB.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. ProductionHUB.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact ProductionHUB.com at [support@productionhub.com](mailto:support@productionhub.com) to request the removal of this information from our database.

**With whom the information may be shared.** back to top

ProductionHUB.com discloses your information to a third party credit authorization company, but they do not use your information for any secondary purposes. We only pass over you personal information to other users when a match between media developers has occurred through our service and you have indicated an interest in contacting them. Otherwise, ProductionHUB.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission.

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?** back to top

ProductionHUB.com, from time to time, sends e-mail regarding our products and services if you indicated upon registration or later that you are interested in receiving offers or information from ProductionHUB.com. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal account information by un-checking the 'keep me informed' box or indicate that you no longer wish to receive such offers and mailings.

**What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information?** back to top

Your account information is password protected so that only you have access to your personal information. We encourage you to not divulge your password to anyone. Remember to log off your computer or close your browser window when you have finished your work to ensure that all others cannot access your personal information and correspondence.

**How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.** back to top

You may change any or all of your information by editing your member profile after signing in. Go to the 'edit listing' function to make changes. If you have forgotten your password, you may request a new password. For all other problems signing in, please contact [support@productionhub.com](mailto:support@productionhub.com). You can also choose to have your member profile eliminated from our database entirely by contacting [support@productionhub.com](mailto:support@productionhub.com).

**Notification of Changes**

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated your account, then you will not be contacted. Nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
